eprocessingnetwork.com 2014-02-09

# eProcessing Network | The Everywhere Processing Network™

Your privacy is important to eProcessing Network. We are providing a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices.

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person. You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with eProcessing Network. Here are some examples of the types of personal information eProcessing Network may collect and how we may use it:

**What personal information we collect:**  

  * When you create an eProcessing Network (ePN) ID, you are securely registering your merchant account on the ePN secure payment processing network or with the ePNMobile app. The information we collect includes your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact preferences, merchant processing ID and banking information for billing purposes.

**How we use your personal information:**

  * The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on eProcessing Network’s latest product announcements and software updates.
  * From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about our network security, software enhancements and updates, and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with eProcessing Network, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.
  * We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve products, services, and customer communications.

### Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information

We also collect non-personal information − data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect and use non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

  * We may collect information such as transaction types and volume, SIC or MCC codes, zip code, or unique device identifiers, location, and the time zone where transactions are sent from when payment transactions are sent to eProcessing Network’s secure payment network. 

If we do combine non-personal information with personal information the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

### Cookies and Other Technologies

eProcessing Network’s secure network does not use cookies and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons per PCI Security Council compliance rules. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

As is true of most websites, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer and enhance the site to ensure a better user experience. eProcessing Network does not distribute this information.

In some of our email messages, we may use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the eProcessing Network website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages.

### Disclosure to Third Parties

**Service Providers**

eProcessing Network does not share personal information with any third party companies unless it is in direct relationship to an associated payment processor who issued the customers merchant processing account ID. These companies are equally obligated to protect your information.

**Others**

It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within your country of residence − for eProcessing Network to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

### Protection of Personal Information

eProcessing Network takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

eProcessing Network online services use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is collected. To login to the ePN merchant resource center (MSC) from these services, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Chrome, Safari, Firefox, or Internet Explorer. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal information while it’s transmitted over the Internet.

### Integrity and Retention of Personal Information

eProcessing Network makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

### Access to Personal Information

You can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by securely logging in to your account at http://www.eprocessingnetwork.com and selecting from the drop down menu – Merchant LogIn. For other personal information, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access so you can request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if eProcessing Network is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law. All access, correction, or deletion requests can be made by emailing: support@eProcessingNetwork.com.

### Third-Party Sites and Services

eProcessing Network websites, products, applications, and services may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. Our products and services may also use or offer products or services from third parties Information collected by third parties, which may include such things as location data or contact details, is governed by their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.

### Our Companywide Commitment to Your Privacy

To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate our privacy and security guidelines to eProcessing Network employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

### Privacy Questions

If you have any questions or concerns about eProcessing Network Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us. 

eProcessing Network may update its Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.

eProcessing Network  
1415 North Loop West  
Suite 1185  
Houston, TX 77008

Last updated: January 14, 2014
